{
    "id": "fc95a337c2804c5c9dcff9c67fbf7f86",
    "title": "Simple present or present continuous?",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "68270bb14c8e49368e9de9f53f8d99f7",
            "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The summer term ………………….. on April 18th.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is starting",
                        "starts"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My plane ………………. at",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "leaves",
                        "is leaving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When …………………. in Bangkok?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is the train arriving",
                        "does the train arrive"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will pay you back when I ………………….. a job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will get",
                        "get",
                        "am getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… to the US next week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "am going"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………….. for a new job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "looks",
                        "is looking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Granny’s train ………………….. at",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "arrives",
                        "is arriving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will tell you if I ………………….. her name.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "know",
                        "knew",
                        "will know"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘What ………………… there?’ ‘I …………………. a cake.’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do you do make",
                        "are you doing am making"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….. Lucia on Tuesday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "am seeing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}